var questions = [{
	"question": "Which of the two countries are separated by McMahon line?",
	"option1": "USA AND CANADA",
	"option2": "PORTUGAL AND SPAIN",
	"option3": "INDIA AND CHINA",
	"option4": "NORTH KOREA AND SOUTH KOREA",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Who was the 1st president of INDIA?",
	"option1": "JAWAHARLAL NEHRU",
	"option2": "APJ ABDUL KALAM",
	"option3": "RAJENDRA PRASAD",
	"option4": "S.RADHAKRISHNAN",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the football club with most champions league titles?",
	"option1": "Fc Barcelona",
	"option2": "Atletico DE Madrid",
	"option3": "Fc Bayern Munich",
	"option4": "Real Madrid",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "In which year did india and Pakistan signed Tashkent agreement?",
	"option1": "1965",
	"option2": "1966",
	"option3": "1963",
	"option4": "None of the above",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "In which year Chernobyl nuclear accident occurred?",
	"option1": "1976",
	"option2": "1983",
	"option3": "1986",
	"option4": "1977",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which was india’s first indigenous fighter jet?",
	"option1": "HAL AJEET",
	"option2": "HAL TEJAS",
	"option3": "HF 24 MARUT",
	"option4": "E2 HAWK EYE",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which footballer holds the record for scoring most goals(91) in a calendar year?",
	"option1": "ROBERT LEWANDOWSKI",
	"option2": "CRISTIANO RONALDO",
	"option3": "LIONEL MESSI",
	"option4": "LUIS SUAREZ",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following countries do not share land border with china?",
	"option1": "NORTH KOREA",
	"option2": "MONGOLIA",
	"option3": "LAOS ",
	"option4": "THAILAND",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "How much percent of area of earth is covered by water?","option1": "81%",
	"option2": "71%",
	"option3": "61%",
	"option4": "51%",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Who has the most number of Olympic gold medals in the world?",
    "option1": "USAIN BOLT",
	"option2": "MICHAEL PHELPS",
	"option3": "PAAVO NURMI",
	"option4": "LARISA LATYNINA",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which is the largest joint in human body?",
	"option1": "KNEE",
	"option2": "PIVOT",
	"option3": "HIP",
	"option4": "HINGE",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "WHO WAS THE FIRST MAN TO CLIMB THE MOUNT EVEREST WITHOUT OXYGEN?",
    "option1": "JUNKO TABEI",
	"option2": "REINHOLD MESSNER",
	"option3": "PETER HABELER",
	"option4": "PHU DORJI",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Who was the first Indian scientist to the noble prize?",
	"option1": "AMARTYA SEN",
	"option2": "HARGOBIND KHURANA",
	"option3": "CV RAMAN",
	"option4": "APJ ABDUL KALAM",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following country is not a member of “THE QUAD” group?",
	"option1": "USA",
	"option2": "SOUTH KOREA",
	"option3": "JAPAN",
	"option4": "INDIA",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "After the collapse of the SOVIET UNION how many countries were formed?",
	"option1": "13",
	"option2": "12",
	"option3": "15",
	"option4": "11",
	"answer": "3"
}];